Guide to the Louis H. Roddis Papers, 1823-1990 RL.01102
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Panel and Committee Reports of ERAB, 1975-1984 and undated
  - 26 D-27 Report on Status of AIS, 1982 (Box 35)
  - 26 E-1 ERAB Conservation, 1981 (Box 35)
  - 26 E-2 Conservation Panel Draft, 1982 May 29 (Box 35)
  - 26 E-3 Energy Reports to Conservation Panel, 1982-1983 (Box 35)
  - 26 E-4 Draft of Conservation Panel Report, 1982 (Box 36)
  - 26 E-5 Draft of Conservation Report, 1982, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - 26 E-6 Conservation Panel Drafts, 1982, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - 26 E-7 Letters Subject to Conservation Panel, 1982-1983 (Box 36)
  - 26 E-9 PyroPowerCorporation Folder, 1982 (Box 36)
  - 26 E-11 The 1983 Renewable Energy Forum, 1983, Jun. 16, 4 folders (Box 36)
  - 26 F-1 ERAB Research and Development Priorities, 1980 Oct. (Box 36)
  - 26 F-2 ERAB Research and Development Priorities, 1980 Dec. 19 (Box 36)
  - 26 F-3 Research and Development, 1981 Jan. 26 (Box 36)
  - 26 F-4 Research and Development Panel Meeting Book, 1981 Jan. 26 (Box 36)
  - 26 F-5 Research and Development Panel Meeting, 1981 Jan. 26 (Box 36)
  - 26 F-6 ERAB Research and Development, 1981 Feb. 5-6 (Box 36)
  - 26 F-7 Federal Energy Research and Development Priorities Meeting, 1981, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - 26 F-8 Federal Energy Research and Development Committee, 1981 (Box 36)
  - 26 F-9 Federal Energy Research and Development Priorities Committte, 1981 (Box 36)
  - 26 F-10 Federal Energy Research and Development Priorities Committee, 1981 Sept. (Box 36)
  - 26 F-11 Federal Energy Research and Development Priorities Committee, 1981 (Box 36)
  - 26 F-12 Federal Energy Research and Development Priorities Committee Transcript, 1981 Sept. 24 (Box 37)
  - 26 F-13 Federal Energy Research and Development Priorities Committee, 1981 (Box 37)
  - 26 F-14 Federal Energy Research and Development Priorities Committe Study Appendices, 1981 Oct. 9 (Box 37)
  - 26 F-15 Federal Energy Reseach and Development Priorities Committee--Seventh Draft Report and Dissents, 1981 Nov. 13 (Box 37)
  - 26 G-1 Conservation Panel Brookhaven National Laboratory (BNL) Meeting, 1979 (Box 37)
  - 26 G-2 Conservation Panel, 1980 (Box 37)
  - 26 G-3 Conservation Panel Research and Development, 1980 (Box 37)
  - 26 G-4 Energy Conservation, 1980 (Box 37)
  - 26 G-5A Rankings of Energy Conservation, 1979 (Box 37)
  - 26 G-7 Technical Base Assessment Conservation Sub-Programs, 1980 (Box 37)
  - 26 G-8 Basic Research in Conservation, 1980 Jun. 6 (Box 37)
  - 26 G-9 Energy Conservation Program Document, 1980 Feb. (Box 37)
  - 26 G-10 Conservation-Building Systems, 1980 Jun. 24 (Box 37)
  - 26 G-11 ERAB-Gas Research Institute (GRI) Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 37)
  - 26 G-12 Review of Gas Research and Development Program, 1980 Jul. 21 (Box 37)
  - 26 G-13 Review Of Gas Research and Development Program Including Five-Year Plan, 1980 Jul. 21 (Box 37)
  - 26 G-15 Weapons Laboratory Study Group No. 1, 1979, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - 26 G-16 Weapons Laboratory Study Group No. 2, 1978-1979, 4 folders (Box 37)
  - 26 G-17 ERAB Report on Construction/Development Project Management 1979 Nov. (Box 38)
  - 26 G-18 Project Management Panel, 1979 (Box 38)
  - 26 G-19 ERAB Defense Wastes No. 1, 1979, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - 26 G-20 Conservation Panel, ERAB Defense Wastes No. 2 1979 (Box 38)
  - 26 G-21 Conservation Panel, DOE Project Managemene, 1979 (Box 38)
  - 26 G-22 Conservation Panel Biomass Draft, 1981 (Box 38)
  - 26 H-1 National Laboratories Panel--Role of Labs, 1981 (Box 38)
  - 26 H-2 National Laboratories Panel Meeting, 1981 (Box 38)
  - 26 H-3 National Laboratories Panel--New York, 1981 (Box 38)
  - 26 H-4 National Laboratories Panel Studies, 1975-1981, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - 26 H-5 Natioanl Laboratories Panel--Sewell Lab Study, 1982 Jan. (Box 38)
  - 26 H-6 National Laboratories Panel--Labs Panel, 1982 (Box 38)
  - 26 H-7 National Laboratories Panel--Preliminary Report Draft, 1982, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - 26 H-8 National Laboratories Panel, 1982 Mar. (Box 38)
  - 26 H-9 National Laboratories Panel, 1982 (Box 38)
  - 26 H-10 National Laboratories Panel, 1982 (Box 38)
  - 26 H-11 National Laboratories Panel Meeting, 1982 Sept, 9-10 (Box 38)
  - 26 H-12 National Laboratories Panel--Progress Report, 1982 Mar. (Box 38)
  - 26 H-13 National Laboratories Panel--Preliminary Report, 1982 Mar. (Box 38)
  - 26 H-14 National Laboratories Panel--Draft Final Report Vol. 1, 1982 Sept. 9 (Box 38)
  - 26 H-15 National Laboratories Panel--Draft Final Report Vol. 2, 1982 Sept. (Box 38)
  - 26 H-16 National Laboratories Panel--Final Draft Report, 1982 Sept. (Box 38)
  - 26 H-17 National Laboratories Panel--Multi-Program Labs, 1982 Sept. (Box 38)
  - 26 I-2 University-Department of Energy Relationships Panel. 1983 (Box 38)
  - 26 I-3 University-Department of Energy Relationships Panel --Programs, 1983 (Box 39)
  - 26 I-4 University-Department of Energy Relationships Panel--Programs 1983 (Box 39)
  - 26 I-5 University-Department of Energy Relationships Panel--Final, 1983 (Box 39)
  - 26 I-7 University-Department of Energy Relationships Panel--Support Studies, 1983 Mar. 21 (Box 39)
  - 26 I-8 University-Department of Energy Relationships Panel--Draft Vol.1, 1983 (Box 39)
  - 26 I-9 University-Department of Energy Relationships Panel--Support Studies Draft Vol.2, 1983 Aug. (Box 39)
  - 26 J-1 Federal Role in Energy Research and Development Panel, 1982, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - 26 J-2 Federal Role in Energy Research and Development Panel--Government Role, 1982, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - 26 J-3 Federal Role in Energy Research and Development Panel--Assessment for Individual Technologies, 1982 Jun. 3 (Box 39)
  - 26 J-4 Federal Role in Energy Research and Development Panel--A Historical Summary, 1982 Sept. 7 (Box 39)
  - 26 J-5 Federal Role in Energy Research and Development Panel, 1982 (Box 39)
  - 26 J-7 Federal Role in Energy Research and Development Panel--Fiscal Year 1983 Budget, 1981 (Box 39)
  - 26 J-8 Federal Role in Energy Research and Development Panel--Report of ERAB, 1983 Feb. (Box 39)
  - 26 J-9 Federal Role in Energy Research and Development Panel--Writing Draft, 1983 Jan. 22 (Box 39)
  - 26 J-10 Federal Role in Energy Research and Development Panel--Final Draft, 1983 Feb. (Box 39)
  - 26 J-11 Federal Role in Energy Research and Development Panel--Final Draft, 1983 Feb. (Box 39)
  - 26 K-1 Light Water Reactors Safety Research and Development--DOE Reports, 1982, 3 folders (Box 39)
  - 26 K-2 Light Water Reactors Safety Research and Development--Technology Panel, 1982-1983 (Box 39)
  - 26 K-3 Light Water Reactors Safety Research and Development--Technology Panel, 1982 Nov. (Box 39)
  - 26 K-4 Light Water Reactor Safety Research and Development, 1982 (Box 39)
  - 26 K-5 Light Water Reactors Safety Research and Development Panel, 1983 (Box 39)
  - 26 K-6 Light Water Reactors Safety Research and Development Panel, 1983 Mar. (Box 39)
  - 26 K-7 Light Water Reactors Safety Research and Development Panel--Draft and Comments, 1983 (Box 39)
  - 26 K-8 Light Water Reactors Safety Research and Development Panel--Final, 1983 (Box 40)
  - 26 K-9 Light Water Reactors Safety Research and Development Panel--Third Stage, 1984 (Box 40)
  - 26 K-10 Light Water Reactors Safety Research and Development Panel, 1984 (Box 40)
  - 26 L-1 Basic Energy Materials Research and Development Panel--Plans for Membership, undated (Box 40)
  - 26 L-2 Basic Energy Materials Research and Development Panel, 1982 (Box 40)
  - 26 L-3 Basic Energy Materials Research and Development Panel, 1984 (Box 40)
  - 26 L-4 Basic Energy Materials Research and Development Panel--Meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 40)
  - 26 L-5 Basic Energy Materials Research and Development Panel, 1979-1983 (Box 40)
  - 26 L-6 Basic Energy Materials Research and Development Panel, 1983 (Box 40)
  - 26 L-7 Basic Energy Materials Research and Development Panel, 1983 (Box 40)
  - 26 L-8 Basic Energy Materials Research and Development Panel--Finals, 1983 (Box 40)
  - 26 L-11 Basic Energy Materials Research and Development Panel--Information on Phillips Petroleum Company, 1982-1983 (Box 40)
- Three Mile Island Accident, 1976-1984 (bulk 1979)
  Includes correspondence, articles, booklets, drafts, statements by the Edison Electric Institute, notes and reports illustrating Roddis's involvement with the investigation of the accident. Also contains the "Kemeny Report" which looks at every aspect of the incident, reports to the President's Commission on the accident at Three Mile Island, and a subpoena for Roddis and his deposition. The materials document the nuclear accident and its cleanup, look at public health issues, training of personnel to work at a nuclear plant, control issues, and the effect the Three Mile Island Accident had on nuclear power plant safety. Arranged by Roddis's index codes. Series continues in boxes 98-100.
  - 27-2 Summary of the Report of the Public's Right to Information Task Force, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-3 Technical Staff Report on Public Health and Epidemiology, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-4 Report of the Office of Chief Counsel on the Nuclear Regulatory Commision, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-5 Summary of the Public Health and Safety Task Force Report, 1979 Oct.31 (Box 40)
  - 27-6 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Pilot Operated Relief Valve (PORV) Design and Performance, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-7 Report of the Office of the Chief Counsel on Emergency Preparedness, 1979 Oct.31 (Box 40)
  - 27-8 Report of the Office of Chief Counsel on Emergency Response, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-9 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Transport of Radioactivity, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-10 Technical Staff Analysis Summary, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-11 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Iodine Filter Performance, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-12 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Quality Assurance, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-13 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Core Damage, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-14 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Thermal Hydraulics, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-15 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Chemistry, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-16 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Condensate Polisher, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-17 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Alternate Event Sequences, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-18 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Closed Emergency Feedwater Valves, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-19 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Technical Assessment of Operating, Abnormal, and Emergency Procedures, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-20 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Behavioral Effects, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-21 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Central Room Design and Performance, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-22 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Selection, Training, Qualifications, and Licensing of Operating Personnel, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 40)
  - 27-23 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Wash 1400 Reactor Safety Study, 1979 Oct.31 (Box 40)
  - 27-24 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Summary Sequence of Events, 1979 Oct.31 (Box 41)
  - 27-25 Technical Staff Analysis Report on Quality Assurance, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 41)
  - 27-26 Report of the Office of Chief Counsel on the Role of the Managing Utility and Its Suppliers, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 41)
  - 27-27 Technical Staff Analysis on Radiation Health Effects, 1979 Oct. 31 (Box 41)
  - 27-28 Summary of Task Force Report, 1979 Oct.31 (Box 41)
  - 27-29 Report from President's Commission, 1979 Oct.31 (Box 41)
  - 27-30 Subpoena and testificandium of Louis H. Roddis, Jr. 1979 Aug. (Box 41)
  - 27-31 Deposition of Louis H. Roddis, Jr., 1979 Aug. 27 (Box 41)
  - 27-39 Nuclear Power Safety After Three Mile Island, 1980 Mar. (Box 41)
  - 27-40 Three Mile Island--A Review, 1980 (Box 41)
  - 27-46 Publicity, 1979-1980 (Box 41)
  - 27-49 Generic Regulatory Developments, 1982 Jan. 22 (Box 41)
  - 27-50 Two Years Later, 1981 (Box 41)
  - 27-51 Power Plant Staffing, 1980 Mar. (Box 41)
  - 27-52 Edison Electric Institute on Three Mile Island Cleanup, 1981 May 5 (Box 41)
  - 27-53 Three Mile Island-2 Funding, 1982-1984 (Box 41)
  - 27-54 Metropolitan Edison Three Mile Island Reports, 1979 (Box 41)
  - 27-55 H.G. Rickover Testimony, 1979 May 24 (Box 41)
  - 27-56 Nuclear Regulatory Commission--Lessons Learned, 1979 (Box 41)
  - 27-57 Three Mile Island Speeches, 1979 (Box 41)
  - 27-79 Trip Reports Ad-Hoc Advisory Committee on Personnel Selection and Training and Man-Machine Interface on Communication Package:
    - General Public Utilities (GPU) Commission Consultants Letters, 1979 (Box 41)
    - Trip Report/Agenda, 1979 (Box 41)
    - Ziow and Morris Visit, 1979 Sept. (Box 41)
    - GPU: Ziow and Morris Executive Session, 1979 Sept. (Box 41)
    - Non-Licensed Personel Training, 1979 Oct. 9 (Box 41)
    - Original Drafting Material, 1979 Sept. 28 (Box 41)
    - Letter and Enclosure, 1979 Sept. 9 (Box 41)
    - Duke/GPU Training, 1979 (Box 41)
    - Nuclear Safety Analysis Center (NSAC) Training Input, 1979 (Box 41)
    - Common Wealth Edison Report, 1979 (Box 41)
    - Louis H. Roddis Letters, 1979 Aug. (Box 41)
    - Three Mile Island Analysis, 1979 (Box 41)
    - Three Mile Island Involving Laney, 1979 (Box 41)
    - Letter from Louis H. Roddis to Herman Dieckamp,, President of GPU 1979 Sept. 9 (Box 41)
    - Information from Visits, 1979 (Box 41)
    - Pass-Outs Second Set, 1979 (Box 41)
    - GPU No. 2 (1P#2) Visit, 1979 Sept. 10 (Box 41)
    - 1P#2 for GPU, 1979 Sept. 10 (Box 41)
    - GPU Resumes, 1979 (Box 41)
    - Interim GPU Report Drafts, 1979 Nov. 9 (Box 41)
    - GPU Meetings, 1979-1981 (Box 41)
  - 27-80 Trip Reports Ad-Hoc Advisory Committee on Personnel Selection and Training and Man-Machine Interface on Communication Package: (Box 42)
    - GPU Meeting, 1979 (Box 42)
    - Interim Report on Personnel Selection and Training Man-Machine Communications, 1979 Nov. 26 (Box 42)
    - Trans World Airlines (TWA), 1979 Nov. 27 (Box 42)
    - Trip Report, 1979 Nov. 26-28 (Box 42)
    - Maintenance Training, 1979 (Box 42)
    - GPU Conference, 1979, July 13 (Box 42)
    - Material Received, 1980 (Box 42)
    - Information on Synthetic Fuels 1978-1979 (Box 42)
    - Information from General Public Utilities Service Corporation, 1979 (Box 42)
    - Johnson Space Flight Center, 1979 (Box 42)
    - Houston Original Trip Reports, 1979 Dec. 10-11 (Box 42)
    - General Public Utilities Committees, 1979 July (Box 42)
  - 27-81 GPU Draft, 1979 (Box 42)
  - 27-81 General Public Utilities Final Report Draft, 1979-1980 (Box 42)
  - 27-81 General Public Utilities Comments, 1980 (Box 42)
  - 27-82 Report of the AD-HOC Advisory Committee on Personnel Selection and Training Man-Machine Interface and Communication, 1980 Jan. (Box 42)
  - 27-83 Action Status on Recommendations of the AD-HOC Advisory Committee, 1981 Feb. 6 (Box 42)
  - 27-84 AIF Speech, 1981 Oct. 19 (Box 42)
  - 27-85 Simulation in Training for Nuclear Power Plant Operators, 1979 Aug. (Box 42)
  - 27-86 Background Reports Furnished by the AD-HOC Committee, 1978-1979, 2 folders (Box 42)
  - 27-87 TWA Training Materials, 1976-1979 (Box 42)
  - 27-88 Commonwealth Edison Company, 1979 (Box 42)
  - 27-89 Amoco Chemicals Corporation Information, 1977-1979 (Box 42)
  - 27-90 Gould Government Systems, 1979 (Box 42)
  - 27-91 TVA Power Operations Training Center, 1979 (Box 42)
- Anti-Trust Cases, 1970-1973, 1976-1977
  This series documents three anti-trust cases brought before the Securities and Exchange Commission: United Technologies Corporation (UTC) v. Babcock and Wilcox Company (B&W), United States of America v. United Technologies Corporation, and Columbus and Southern Ohio Electric Company (C&S) v. American Electric Power (AEP). The materials consist of memorandums and court reports, transcripts of proceedings, Roddis'ss testimonies in each case, affidavits, clippings of the trials, supporting documents to the cases, notes, briefs, and decisions. B&W brought UTC to court because of UTC's attempted takeover. US took UTC to court for its proposed tender offer for all of the outstanding common stock of the B&W. C&S v. AEP concerns AEP wanting to exchange its common stock shares with C&S's outstanding common stock shares. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 28 A-1 Babcock & Wilcox Company vs. United Technologies Corporation Complaint, 1977, April 4 (Box 42)
  - 28 A-2 Babcock & Wilcox Company vs. United Technologies Corporation Defendant's Pretrial Memorandum, 1977, May 25 (Box 42)
  - 28 A-3 Babcock & Wilcox Company vs. United Technologies Corporation Trial Memorandum on the Anti-Trust and Atomic Energy Acts Issues, 1977 (Box 42)
  - 28 A-4 Babcock & Wilcox Company vs. United Technologies Corporation Defendant's Proposed Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law, 1977 June 8 (Box 42)
  - 28 A-5 Babcock & Wilcox Company vs. United Technologies Corporation Plaintiff's Proposed Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law, 1977 June 8 (Box 43)
  - 28 A-6 Babcock & Wilcox Company vs. United Technologies Corporation Post-Trial Memorandum, 1977 June (Box 43)
  - 28 A-7 Babcock & Wilcox Company vs. United Technologies Corporation Plaintiff's Post-Trial Brief on the Anti-Trust Issue, 1977 June 8 (Box 43)
  - 28 A-8 Babcock & Wilcox Company vs. United Technologies Corporation Memorandum Opinion and Order by Judge Contie, 1977 July 15 (Box 43)
  - 28 A-9 Babcock & Wilcox Company vs. United Technologies Corporation Judgement by Judge Contie, 1977 July 15 (Box 43)
  - 28 A-10 Babcock & Wilcox Company vs. United Technologies Corporation U.S. Court of Appeals for 6th Circuit Affidavit NO. 77-3383, 1977 (Box 43)
  - 28 A-12 Newspaper Clippings, 1977 (Box 43)
  - 28 A-13 Testimony and Exhibitions (Other than Louis H. Roddis, Jr.), 1977 (Box 43)
  - 28 A-14 Notes on Louis H. Roddis, Jr. Testimony, 1977, 3 folders (Box 43)
  - 28 A-27 Report for United Technologies Corporation, 1976 Jun. 1 (Box 43)
  - 28 A-28 Internal Report of Babcock & Wilcox, 1976 Sept. 20 (Box 43)
  - 28 A-31 Electricity Report of Analytical Group Topics No. 20, 1977 (Box 43)
  - 28 A-32 Outlook for Supply/Demand of Electricity, 1977 April (Box 43)
  - 28 B-1 Memorandum on Civil Action C77-268A, 1977 Aug. 27 (Box 43)
  - 28 B-2 Post-Trial Memorandum, 1977 Aug. 27 (Box 43)
  - 28 B-3 Miscellaneous on Louis H. Roddis, Jr. Testimony, 1977, 3 folders (Box 43)
  - 28 B-4 US-UT Papers on Gasification, 1977 (Box 43)
  - 28 B-5 United States of America vs. United Technologies Corporation, 1977 (Box 43)
  - 28 C-1 SEC Testimony of Louis H. Roddis, Jr. in AEP-Columbus & Southern Case Vol. 1, 1970-1971 (volume) (Box 43)
  - 28 C-2 Supporting Documents in AEP-Columbus & Southern Case Vol. 2, 1970-1971 (volume) (Box 43)
  - 28 C-3 Briefs & Decisions in AEP-Columbus & Southern Case Vol. 3, 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - 28 C-4 Columbus & Southern and American Electric Power--Copied Clippings from a Book, 1971 (Box 44)
- Other Government Agencies Material Series, 1973-1982
  Consists of articles, correspondence, reports, writings, studies, notes, press releases, legislation, and congressional records pertaining to fertilizers, government regulation of energy prices, the structure of agencies and their policies. Government agencies include the Federal Energy Administration (FEA), the Department of Energy (DOE), the Atomic Energy Commission (AEC), and the Federal Energy Research and Development Administration. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 30-1 NSC Fertilizer, 1974 Aug. 1 (Box 44)
  - 30-2 FEA Legislation, 1974 (Box 44)
  - 30-3 FEA-Role of the Federal Government in Automotive Research and Development, 1974 Nov. 6 (Box 44)
  - 30-4 FEA and Related Activities, 1975-1977 (Box 44)
  - 30-5 Federal Energy Administration--Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 44)
  - 30-6 Federal Energy Research and Development Council, 1973 (Box 44)
  - 30-7 FEA: Memos to Howell. 1977 Apr. (Box 44)
  - 30-8 Energy Systems Task Force Research and Development Committee; Federal Power Commission / National Power Survey, 1973-1975 (Box 44)
  - 30-9 Federal Energy Administration / Office of Energy Research and Development Policy, 1974-1975 (Box 44)
  - 30-10 Department of Energy Organization, 1977 Jan. 27 (Box 44)
  - 30-12 Atomic Energy Commission, 1974 (Box 44)
  - 30-13 Federal Energy Administration Strategies Petroleum Reserve Office (SPRO) Comments, 1977 Mar. 30 (Box 44)
  - 30-15 Energy Research and Development Administration Legislation No.1, 1974 (Box 44)
  - 30-16 Energy Research and Development Administration Legislation No. 2, 1973-1976 (Box 44)
  - 30-17 National Security Council, 1973-1976 (Box 44)
  - 30-20 Department of Energy Reorganization, 1982 (Box 44)
  - 30-21 High Voltage Test Laboratory Proposal and Comments, 1980, 2 folders (Box 44)
  - 30-21 High Voltage Test Laboratory Proposal and Comments, 1980, 1 folder (Box 45)
- Other, 1956-1980 (bulk 1970s)
  This series contains Roddis's unpublished draft The Electric Utility Decisions Process As It Bears on the Selection of Nuclear Power Systems of Different Types which he researched and wrote to assist the Library of Congress in the preparation of a report on aspects of alternative breeder fuel cycles. Included also are reports, correspondence, legal briefs, cases, articles, booklets, writings, and maps that he used to support his data in the Library of Congress report, miscellaneous information on Florida Power and Light, and his consultant work for Electric Power Research Institute. Arranged by Roddis's index codes.
  - 32A-1 Unpublished Congressional Research ServiceDraft and Supporting Data; Congressional Research Service of Library of Congress Contract; Congressional Research Service-78-43-3, 1978 Mar. (Box 45)
  - 32 A-2 Unpublished Congressional Research Service Draft and Supporting Data; Draft of Congressional Research Service-78-43-3, 1978 (Box 45)
  - 32 A-3 Library of Congress Proposal (Other Unpublished (Box 45)
  - Congressional Research Service Drafts and Supporting Data), 1977 (Box 45)
  - 32 A-4 Library of Congress Letters, 1978 (Box 45)
  - 32 A-5 Subcommittee on Fossil and Nuclear Energy Research (Box 45)
  - Development and Demonstration, U.S. House of Representatives, 1978 Feb. 2 (Box 45)
  - 32 A-7 Unpublished Congressional Research Service Draft and Supporting Data--Comparing New Techniques fo the Electric Utilities, 1976 Dec. 9 (Box 45)
  - 32 A-12 Unpublished Congressional Research Service Draft and Supporting Data Institutional Considerations in the Commercialization of Nuclear Technology, 1977 July 1 (Box 45)
  - 32 A-14 Current 1977 Technical Articles 1, 1977 (Box 45)
  - 32 A-15, Current 1977 Technical Articles 2, 1977 (Box 45)
  - 32 A-16, Current 1976-1977 Technical Articles 3, 1976-1977 (Box 45)
  - 32 A-17, Current Atomic Industrial Forum Reports, 1977 (Box 45)
  - 32 B-1, Florida Power and Light Contracts, Power Supply to Wellington, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
  - 32 B-2, Florida Power and Light Contracts, Literature on Wellington Village, 1977 (Box 45)
  - 32 B-3, Florida Power and Light Contracts, 1977 and undated (Box 45)
  - 32 B-4, Florida Power and Light Contracts, Financial Data, 1977 (Box 45)
  - 32 B-6, Florida Power and Light Contracts, Load Forecast, 1977, Sept. 23 (Box 45)
  - 32 B-9, Pennsylvania-New Jersey-Maryland (PJM) Interconnection - Mid-Atlantic Area Coordination (MAAC) Fuel Conservation Agreement, 1977, April (Box 45)
  - 32 B-10, Florida Power and Light Contracts, PJM Interconnection Supplemental Agreement, 1956, Sept. 26 and 1977, Nov. 11 (Box 45)
  - 32 B-11, Florida Power and Light Contracts, PJM Interconnection Agreement, 1956, Nov. 4 (Box 45)
  - 32 B-12, Florida Power and Light Contracts, PJM Interconnection Supplemental Agreement, 1974, April 1 (Box 45)
  - 32 B-13, Florida Power and Light Contracts, New York Power Pool Operating Policy, 1969-1977 (Box 45)